https://www.mtairynews.com/cookie-policy-us

December 11, 2020
Search for:
HomeCookie Policy (US)
This page was last changed on June 19, 2020, last checked on June 19, 2020 and applies to citizens of the United States. 1. IntroductionOur website, https://www.mtairynews.com (hereinafter: “the website”) uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. You do have the right to opt-out and to object against the further use of non-functional cookies.5.1 Manage your consent settingsYou can also disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Advertising cookiesOn this website we use advertising cookies, enabling us to personalize the advertisements for you, and we (and third parties) gain insights into the campaign results. This happens based on a profile we create based on your click and surfing on and outside https://www.mtairynews.com. With these cookies you, as website visitor are linked to a unique ID, so you do not see the same ad more than once for example.You can object to the tracking by these cookies by clicking the “Revoke cookie consent” button.6.3 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook, Twitter and Disqus to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook, Twitter and Disqus. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook, Twitter and Disqus themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook, Twitter and Disqus are located in the United States.7. Placed cookiesGoogle Tag Manager
We use Google Tag Manager for website statistics. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
cto_bundle
Statistics
uslk_inital_url
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.Google Ads Optimization
We use Google Ads Optimization for showing advertisements. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
google_experiment_mod*
3 months
Store and track visits across websites
google_experiment_mod*
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Ads Optimization Privacy Policy.Google Adsense
We use Google Adsense for showing advertisements. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
google_ama_settings
persistent
Store performed actions on the website
google_adsense_settings
persistent
Enable ad delivery or retargeting
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Adsense Privacy Policy.Google Ads
We use Google Ads for advertising. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
goog_pem_mod
persistent
Enable ad delivery or retargeting
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Ads Privacy Policy.Loggly
We use Loggly for website performance optimization. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics
logglytrackingsession
session
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.Google Analytics
Store time of visit
Statistics (anonymous)
_ga
2 years
_gid
1 day
Count and track pageviews
_gat
1 minute
Filter requests from bots
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Policy.Complianz
We use Complianz for cookie consent management. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
cmplz_choice
365 days
Store if a message has been dismissed
Sharing
For more information, please read the Complianz Privacy Policy.Google Fonts
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
Google Fonts API
none
Request user IP address
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Policy.Google reCAPTCHA
We use Google reCAPTCHA for spam prevention. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
rc::c
session
Filter requests from bots
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google reCAPTCHA Privacy Policy.Google Maps
We use Google Maps for maps display. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
Google Maps API
none
Request user IP address
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Maps Privacy Policy.YouTube
We use YouTube for video display. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
GPS
session
Store location data
Sharing
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Policy.Facebook
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
actppresence
1 year
Manage ad display frequency
_fbc
Sharing
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Policy.Twitter
We use Twitter for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
local_storage_support_test
persistent
Load balancing functionality
Marketing/Tracking
metrics_token
persistent
Store if the user has seen embedded content
Sharing
For more information, please read the Twitter Privacy Policy.Criteo
We use Criteo for remarketing. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
criteo_pt_cdb_metrics
criteo_fast_bid_standalone_expires
criteo_fast_bid_standalone
Sharing
For more information, please read the Criteo Privacy Policy.Comscore
We use Comscore for advertising. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
s1
5 years
Sharing
For more information, please read the Comscore Privacy Policy.Matomo
We use Matomo for website statistics. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics (anonymous)
_pk_id*
13 months
Store a unique user ID
_pk_id*
13 months
Store a unique user ID
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.Segment
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.Atlassian Jira Servicedesk
We use Atlassian Jira Servicedesk for customer support management. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
ajs_user_id
ajs_group_id
Statistics
ajs_anonymous_id
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
you may submit a request for access to the data we process about you;
you may object to the processing;
you may request an overview, in a commonly used format, of the data we process about you;
you may request correction or deletion of the data if it is incorrect or not or no longer relevant, or to ask to restrict the processing of the data.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this cookie statement. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our cookie policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Adams Media
319 North Renfro Street
Mount Airy, NC
27030
United States
Website: https://www.mtairynews.com
Email: shurley@mtairynews.com
Phone number: 336-786-4141This cookie policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on December 10, 2020
Cookie Policy (US)
Privacy statement (US)
Disclaimer
© 2018 The Mount Airy News
